Contact

quia322@sbcglobal.net

www.linkedin.com/in/tequia-s-williams-a411928a (LinkedIn) www.pruningdubiety.etsy.com (Company) www.facebook.com/pruningdubiety (Other) www.instagram.com/pruningdubiety (Other)

Top Skills

Registered Nurses
Nursing
Acute Care

Tequia S Williams

Wreath Designer at Pruning Dubiety, LLC and Travel Registered Nurse

Charlotte, North Carolina

Summary

I am a Registered Nurse with ten years of experience and the owner of Pruning Dubiety, LLC, which specializes in wreath designs. We offer spring, summer, and fall door decor as well as wedding specific wreath designs! The link to my Etsy Shop is below under Contact Info. Feel free to visit! Thanks in advance.

http://www.pruningdubiety.etsy.com

Experience

TotalMed Staffing, Inc.
Travel Registered Nurse
January 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months)

Pruning Dubiety, LLC
Owner and Wreath Designer
May 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Charlotte, North Carolina Area

Travel Nurse Across America
Travel Registered Nurse
December 2016 - October 2017 (11 months)

Cirrus Medical Staffing
Travel Registered Nurse
January 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 10 months)
Charlotte, North Carolina Area

Novant Health Registered Nurse July 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 2 months) Manage nursing care within a medical-surgical unit, ranging from five to six patients with general medical, pre-operative, post-operative, orthopedic, stroke, hospice, and long-term care needs.

Presence Health Registered Nurse July 2010 - July 2013 (3 years 1 month)

Manage nursing care within a medical-surgical unit, ranging from five to nine patients with general medical, pre-operative, post-operative, hospice, and long-term care needs.

Education

Northern Illinois University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2006 - 2009)